HAPPY GRADUATION!
Kyoka, congrats on graduating!
Congrats!
Thank you so much, everyone.
When do you get to turn human?
In two days' time.
With the scholarship I received
from the director,
I'll be moving next to the dance school.
Huh?
Kyoka, is that...
It's a commemorative gift
for graduating students.
Even after I become human
and lose my memories of this place,
wearing this ring will let me remember
it all and enter the school barrier.
Mr. Hitoma.
Thank you for everything
over the past year.
You've worked hard, Minazuki.
When you told me about your
shortcomings, it was a revelation.
I had longed to be perfect,
but being imperfect is fine.
And helping each other to overcome those
imperfections is what makes one human.
Yeah, that's right.
Mr. Hitoma.
Thank you for teaching me
what it is to be human.
Minazuki.
Thanks for letting me be your teacher.
EPISODE 7: THE MISANTHROPE AND THE FRUITLESS LOVE FORTUNE
That marks the end of another school year!
Cheers, everyone!
Cheers!
Oh, you're too kind.
I haven't had drinks
with co-workers in so long.
Mr. Hitoma.
Your cup's looking empty.
Oh, thank you.
Have some, too, Ms. Saotome.
Oh, I prefer this.
Sake?
Ms. Yuki, control yourself.
How many bottles have you had?
Um...
You sure do drink like a fish.
Didn't you promise to hold back
when we're in public?
We only get to celebrate
like this once a year!
Stop making excuses.
Just look at the shock
on Mr. Hitoma's face.
What?
You've got the wrong idea!
I used to be a yuki-onna
who lived in a cold region,
which is why I can hold my liquor!
What? You used to be a yuki-onna?!
Did I never mention it?
Were you aware of this, Mr. Hoshino?
Well, yes.
Mr. Hoshino, were you a non-human as well?
No, I've always been human.
That reminds me, I was drinking
when we first met, Mr. Hoshino.
When I got stranded up
on a snowy mountain.
I saw a woman in a kimono holding a
sake bottle and thought I was a goner.
How mean!
That brings back memories, though.
The moment I fell in love at first sight.
What?
I didn't expect you to follow me all
the way to America after that.
Huh? Hey, um...
Would the two of you happen to be...
We're married.
Husband and wife?!
So that handkerchief I stained was a gift
from Ms. Saotome to Mr. Hoshino?
Oh, it all makes sense now...
Finally, my own place
in the staff dormitory!
An apartment with an eight-tatami bedroom
and twelve-tatami living-dining space!
And all for the stellar rent of 20,000
yen per month, utilities included!
A corner room on the top floor.
And no one's moved in below or next door,
so I can be loud as I want!
It's a paradise for a gamer like me!
I'm here to visit.
How'd you know I moved in?
Mr. Hitoma, thanks for your
hard work over the past year.
Why are you here?
I bet it was pretty different
from your last school.
What'd you think?
What kind of question is that?
Are you supposed to be my co-worker?
Well, how was it?
Think you'll still stay on?
Let me think.
A lot happened,
but I had a decent time.
I see. Good to hear it.
Oh, and the principal wants to see you.
What?! Tell me that first!
There's someone I'd like you to meet.
None other than the director
of Shiranui High School.
The director?
She's waiting in the director's office.
Come with me, and I'll introduce you.
U-Understood.
Pardon us.
We're here.
Haneda?
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. Hitoma.
I was happy to hear your time
at this school has been decent.
Let me formally introduce you.
This is our director, Lady Shiranui.
She happens to be a phoenix.
The most powerful being,
who reigns over all of existence.
A phoenix?
And I am a crow tengu.
What?
I can see a month into the future,
albeit in fragments.
Thus, I knew you would
do well at this school,
which is why I decided to hire you.
See into the future?
Sorry to take you by surprise.
Tobari Haneda is a form I take
to observe the students more intimately.
Um, D-Director?
How should I be treating
you going forward?
The way you always have, if you would.
As a precaution, let me warn you
that I'll fire you if you reveal who I am.
The same goes for whoever finds out.
May I ask who else knows about this?
Just me and Haruka, the school nurse.
That reminds me.
Last fall, you were worried
when I had fallen ill.
Thanks for your concern back then.
Oh, I'd forgotten all about that.
I always exhaust myself every year
preparing for the new students.
So that's what it was.
When I first established this school,
it was nothing more than on a whim.
But over time, I began to enjoy it.
I love seeing mortal
beings try their best.
That's why I decided to enroll
as a student to become human.
My goal is to turn human so
I can draw my last breath.
Watching them made me want to live
for the sake of facing death.
I see...
Hey, Mr. Hitoma. Do you like humans?
Humans are selfish and
don't care about others.
Good people are taken advantage
of, and honesty gets you nowhere.
I hate humans.
I may hate humans, but I think
I'm fine with that for now.
Sure.
Here's to a new school year.
ADVANCED CLASS
Okay, first day of the new term.
Last year, it was a Soran Bushi dance...
I love you!
Mr. Rei! Please marry me!
What?!
Hmph!
What's the big idea, Sui?
Karin, stop destroying
the moral fiber of our classroom!
And Hitoma, you're a teacher,
so stop blushing!
I'm in the middle of talking
to the teacher.
Could you please pipe down, Sui?
What?!
What a riot.
Mr. Hitoma, aren't you going to
respond to Karin's proposal?
Huh? Um...
I want two kids!
Where'd that come from?!
Ah, well...
Sorry, but I can't marry you.
Why not?!
Huh? What kind of...
I mean, first off.
You're just messing with me, aren't you?
Not at all!
I really love you, Mr. Rei!
What?
Mr. Rei, please believe me.
No, I won't be led astray.
I know! I'll recite all
of the Japanese eras.
Taika, Hakuchi, Shucho, Taiho, Keiun, Wado
Mr. Rei? Mr. Rei!
– Tenpyo-shoho, Tenpyo-hoji...
– He's frozen up.
Okay. Let's move on to our first
homeroom of the new school year.
First, let's introduce ourselves...
Kurosawa, wake up.
Who're you?
The advanced class homeroom
teacher, Rei Hitoma.
I see...
Hey, wake up!
Oh, are you feeling unwell?
I'm fine.
That's good...
In that case, hang in there
just a little longer.
We'll be done after a short talk.
Let's continue our introductions.
My name is Rei Hitoma.
I teach social studies.
This is my second year being
in charge of the advanced class.
I hope we can have a great year together.
Thanks.
Now for...
Let me introduce myself first!
I'm Karin Ryuzaki, and I just moved up
to the advanced class.
I belong to the noble dragon family.
I want to become human to find love.
So Mr. Rei, will you teach me about love?
Not happening.
Grr...
I haven't set off
the right event flag yet?
I will not give up!
I'll ensure that you fall in love
and agree to marry me!
Just you wait!
Okay, you're up next, Nezu.
You got it!
I'm Machi! Machi Nezu!
I'm a mouse!
I want to become human so
I can eat lots of tasty food!
What a simple-minded reason.
Something tasty I ate lately is
our dorm mom Ryouko's homemade pudding!
The trend nowadays is silky-soft pudding,
but Ryouko's is on the firmer side
with a rich, milky flavor,
not to mention how you
can really taste the eggs!
Sounds more like a food review
than an introduction.
Next, Kurosawa.
Neneko Kurosawa. Cat.
My reason for wanting
to become human... is a secret.
Neneko wouldn't tell the intermediate
class last year why she wants to be human.
I never knew that.
Neneko's always been like that.
Putting on an act
because she thinks it's cool—
Huh? What is it?
What do you want?
S-Say something!
I—
So scary!
Help me, Mr. Hitoma!
She's so scary!
I didn't say anything yet.
You were flashing your fangs at me!
You definitely want to gobble me up!
You're paranoid.
And I bet you taste bad, Machi.
That ticks me off in its own way!
Good morning.
Good morning!
Mr. Rei! I love you!
You're supposed to greet
people with "good morning."
By the way, wanna marry me?
Not really.
Boo...
Take this!
Th-Th-This feeling on my back...
What's up, Mr. Hitoma? You look so funny!
Ohgami. Help me.
I get it. You're killing me here!
Karin-rin, are you down bad
for Mr. Hitoma?
Like, serious serious?
Or do you just think it's funny to toy
with him like Isaki?
I'm downright serious.
Omigosh, that's adorbs!
Karin-rin's, like, so cute!
Loving it. You go, girl!
It's the first time I've seen you
like this, but you're pretty funny.
For real? Thanks!
Hope you vibe with both Isaki and Isaki!
Can you get off me already?
See you all tomorrow.
Hey Karin-rin, tell me more about
that natural makeup from before!
You mean the cosmetics from ancient times?
Sure thing.
Oh, I need to talk to you, Ryuzaki.
Can you spare a moment right now?
What?!
You want to confess your love, Mr. Rei?!
You know that's not it.
Karin-rin, I'll be waiting for you.
Sure!
– Ryuzaki.
– Y-Yes?
About this morning.
You shouldn't be so clingy with me,
so let's not do that.
Also, I don't know how serious you are,
but I can't go along with it,
so I'd like you to stop
with the sudden declarations of love.
You see why, right? So please.
I don't wanna.
I don't wanna, I don't wanna!
I won't stop telling you
that I love you, Mr. Rei!
Huh? But why?
Since I'm in love with you, of course!
Why me, of all people?
Well...
Mr. Rei, remember when you
snuck off campus with Sui?
What?!
I was tailing Sui that day.
That's when I saw you, Mr. Rei.
Back then, you were absolutely stunning.
Despite looking hesitant,
you chose to leave school with Sui, right?
I want to become human to find love.
I want to find love
to be cherished by someone.
Seeing you take action for your student,
all while hesitating,
I couldn't help but fall in love.
Isn't it lame to be so hesitant?
Your reservations show
that you gave it some thought.
I can't think of anything cooler.
Really laying it on there, huh?
Mr. Rei, you're a wonderful
human who cherishes others.
Long ago...
I knew a human just like that.
It was an era when I could
still live close to humans.
I inhabited a cave in the mountains,
spending my days warding off the humans
and animals that'd wander in.
I may have been alone,
but I led a comfortable life.
Until one day, an injured human
princess appeared before me.
The princess cherished me so.
I learned from her
how nice it feels to be petted.
To this day, I still remember
our final day together.
A prince from a neighboring
kingdom showed up.
He was under the impression that I had
kidnapped the princess to hold captive.
And so he brought a large
number of soldiers to my cave.
Since they took up swords against me,
I had no choice but to fight,
but human attacks
were completely ineffective on me.
When I was about
to wipe out the prince's army,
the princess began to plead with me.
"Please don't hurt the poor
prince any longer," she said.
The princess left with the prince
to return to human society...
Paying no mind to what would become of me.
It was then that I first felt it.
I was jealous of the prince.
Cherished by the princess,
protected by her, in her embrace.
Had I been weak like him,
would the princess have stayed by my side?
I was unmatched in my strength,
which is why no one thought to cherish me.
The ages passed, and humans
spread across the globe.
So that I would not harm them,
I began living where no humans approached.
That's when I first heard it.
Rumors of the keeper of the sea's daughter
who went off to a school to become human.
You mean Minazuki?
I knew then that I'd found it.
By becoming human, I could
stand on equal footing with them.
To stay by their side forever.
To be cherished by them!
I yearned for their affection.
I want to become human
and live a life where I fall in love.
You treat people honestly,
even those who aren't human.
You listen to what we
have to say as equals.
That's why I love you,
and want to be loved by you.
It has to be you, Mr. Rei.
Ryuzaki.
Sorry. It still stands
that I'm your teacher.
You can't make advances on a student?
That's part of it.
I care for you and the rest of my students
solely as a teacher.
So it wouldn't be right to treat one of
you as special by, say, falling in love.
If you're going to push me away,
then at least be firm about it.
Sorry.
I understand. I'm sorry for bothering you.
It's fine. I'm used to being alone.
Ryuzaki.
I won't fall in love with you.
But romantic feelings aren't
the only reason to stay by someone's side.
As your teacher, I don't
want to see you all alone.
Until the day comes that you graduate.
You really don't play fair, Mr. Rei.
That said, I still
can't help but love you.
So until I graduate
and leave this school as a human,
don't make me give up
on my love for you.
You just said you don't want to
see me all alone, didn't you?
Ryuzaki...
I don't need to hear your answer.
I'll see you tomorrow!
Hey, wait!
He turned me down!
Karin-rin, you did everything you could.
Good job.
We can talk it out all you like.
Yeah. Yeah!
Good morning!
I should stop gaming until the last minute
just because the dorm's so close...
Mr. Rei! Good morning!
Oh, Ryuzaki. Morning.
I love you today, too!
NEXT EPISODE: THE MISANTHROPE AND THE MAGIC FOR PEACE AND QUIET